I'm sorry
Daniel
He's him and you're you
You don't have to apologize for him
Cynthia
We don't blame you
All right
Don't be sad over someone
who isn't worth it
The food is getting cold
Sit down and eat
Here's my plan for the money
Pay off the debt first
With the rest of the money
I want to expand the scale
And increase production
Okay Lewes
As long as you have a plan
Right
We all support you
My gold bracelet
My big gold watch
I heard Daniel
Lost over six million
Now he's selling cars
and gold to raise money
Oh my
What did I do to deserve this
My big gold bracelet
Haven't you embarrassed us enough
Go back inside
Isn't that Lewes
Lewes
Is this your new car